就是很簡單啊
It's very simple.
要是兩個人處的不好
When a person is in a relationship that isn't great,
當然是分手
they get out of it.
《春心蕩漾》上季回顧
Last season on "Mistresses".
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
我不干了  莫娜  想要我的小青蛙嗎
I'm quitting, Mona. Do you want my frog?
當然
Yes.
真不敢相信我終于當上了店主
I can't believe I finally own this shop.
海邊之家
都是我的了
It's all mine.
你真是世界上最好的媽媽
You're the best mom in the world.
凱倫  萬一有人知道
Karen, if anyone finds out
你和患者有染
that you were sleeping with your patient,
你會失去執照的
you could lose your license.
這是我們的兒子山姆
This is our son, sam.
金醫生是爸爸的心理醫生
Dr. Kim was dad's therapist.
你愛上她了  山姆  是嗎
You love her, Sam, don't you?
和你父親一樣
Just like your father did.
山姆  山姆  不要
Sam! Sam, no!
我昨晚跟別人睡了
I cheated on Harry last night.
-是誰  -是個同事  叫多米尼克
- Who? - This guy from work, Dominic.
哈利  我懷孕了  但寶寶可能不是你的
I'm pregnant, Harry, but it might not be yours.
我愛你
I love you.
我愛你很久了
I have for a long time.
你現在依然是我的愛人  我選擇你  薩維
You're still my love. I choose you, Savi.
-薩維  -快來人啊
- Savi? - We need help over here!
-是我姐姐  -急救
- It's my sister! - -Code blue.
八個月后
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯：冰藍  愛卿遛小鳥  幸田實果子
■
翻譯：lisa0228  屯栗子  Michael  圈圈
初校：Michael  圈圈  蓬蓬裙  蘋果果
■
時間軸：coco  沒有影子    后期：MythCreator    監制：蘋果果
是個男孩
薩繆爾·格雷
薩維  你妹妹來了
Savi, your sister's here.
準備好走了嗎
You ready to go?
當然
Absolutely.
春
心 蕩 漾
第二季第一集
姑娘們  姑娘們
Ladies, ladies.
敬健康證明書
A toast to a clean bill of health,
物理治療的結束
the end of physical therapy,
還有我不用再開車去馬里布了
and me not having to drive to Malibu anymore.
阿門
Amen.
各位  我要快點說完
Okay, guys, I'm gonna say this quickly,
因為不然我就要哭了
because otherwise I'm gonna cry.
不不不  千萬別哭
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Please don't cry.
因為如果你哭了  我也會哭
Because if you cry, I will cry,
艾普莉絕對會崩潰
and April will totally fall apart.
是的  我會的
It's true. I will.
我可能沒事
I'll probably be okay.
我是那種深藏不露的人
Well, I'm more of a "Cry on the inside" kind of a person.
我只想告訴你們
Well, I just want you guys to know that
如果沒有你們  我是沒法挺過這八個月的
I would not have survived the last eight months without you.
六次手術
Six surgeries --
-不  沒有六次  -有的
- No, not six. - Yes, it was.
脾臟破裂  肝穿孔  肺功能衰竭
Ruptured spleen, pierced liver, collapsed lung --
別忘了短暫昏迷
Oh, don't forget the brief coma.
那是我們進行過的
Those were some of the best conversations
最棒的對話
you and I have ever had.
我的意思是  每次
My point is, is that every time
有一名醫生到我的病房來
another doctor came into my hospital room
告訴我還有更多
and told me that there was more --
更多要做的  要治療的  我想放棄
More to do, more to fix -- I wanted to quit.
但你們中的一個會打電話或者出現
But then one of you would call or show up
或者送來關心包裹
or send a little care package,
我就會記得我為什么如此努力戰斗
and I would remember why I was fighting so hard.
所以我才能痊愈  和你們在一起
And it was so I could be right here with you guys.
所以謝謝你們
So thank you.
謝謝你們救了我的命
Thank you for saving my life.
我們愛你  薩維
We love you, Savi.
我覺得我喝醉了
And...I think I'm drunk.
我要喝咖啡  還有誰要
I'm switching to coffee. Anyone else?
不要了
No.
快點說  你的寶寶派對怎么樣
Okay, quick. How was your baby shower?
天吶  簡直太瘋狂了
Oh, my god. It was ridonks.
挺好啊  這是你辦的第四次宴會了  對吧
That's great. This is your fourth event already, right?
第五次  大部分情況下是幫朋友
Fifth. Mostly for friends,
但我今天要和我不認識的人見面
but I have a meeting today with someone that I don't already know.
-真激動  -什么很激動啊
- So that's exciting. - What's exciting?
艾普莉的約會
April's dating life.
你在和誰約會嗎
Oooh! Are you seeing someone?
我和很多人在約會
I am seeing lots of people.
上網就會這樣
That's what happens when you go online.
那些社會渣滓出現在你家門口
The dregs of society show up at your door
帶你去打迷你高爾夫或者KTV
and take you places like miniature golfing and karaoke bars.
上一個帶我去了農場
The last guy took me to a farm.
那真新穎
That's original.
他讓我愛撫他的豬
He made me pet his pig.
我猜那不是委婉說法
Oh. I'm guessing that's not a euphemism.
不是
No.
真抱歉  是工作電話  我得走了
So sorry, but that's work. I got to go.
我也得走了  我得為見面準備
You know what? I'm gonna go, too. I got to prep for this meeting.
回頭見
Mm, see you later.
愛你
Love you.
-我愛你  -我愛你  好運
- I love you. - I love you. Good luck.
謝謝
Thanks.
你現在要干什么呢
So, what are you gonna do now?
這真是個有價值的問題啊
Well, that's the million-dollar question, isn't it?
當你逃脫死亡時
I mean, when you cheat death,
就該及時行樂  玩個痛快  對吧
you're supposed to carpe diem your face off, right?
但我不確定那是什么樣子  或者如何去做
But I'm not sure what that looks like or how to do it.
等等  我其實是問你今天下午想干什么
Wait. No, I meant what are you gonna do this afternoon?
不好  是換貨人
Oh, no. It's the exchanger.
誰
The who?
這個女人  她每周都過來
This woman, she comes in here every week,
買些東西  下周來換掉
buys something, then comes back the next week to exchange it.
每周哦  薩維  每周
Every week, Savi. Every week.
好吧  去處理吧
Okay, well, go deal.
我就待在這里  把握今天
I'll be right here, seizing the day.
你好啊  是我
Hey, you. It's me.
你現在在干什么呢
What are you doing right now?
我聽說你那天讓弗利醫生印象深刻
I understand you made an impression on Dr. Foley the other day.
-希望是好印象  -是的
- I hope it was a good one. - It was.
你在醫院的工作飽受好評
Your work here at the hospital has been very well received,
但你的執照兩個月前恢復了
but your suspension was lifted over two months ago,
而你完全沒提到
and you still haven't said anything
回到私人診所的事
about returning to private practice.
因為我覺得不會回去了
That's because I don't think I will be.
你更喜歡在急診室工作嗎
You prefer working in the E.R.?
是啊
I do.
你不懷念和病人
You don't miss the opportunity
親密接觸的機會嗎
to delve deeper with your patients?
我很擔心那點  但我這樣開心多了
I was concerned about that, but I'm much happier this way.
我能幫助更多人
I get to help more people.
那在醫院之外呢
What about outside the hospital?
你在約會嗎
Are you dating at all?
我目前對約會沒有興趣
I'm not interested in dating yet.
我在這張沙發的對面坐了很長時間
I've been on the other side of this couch long enough
知道我們是在繞圈
to know what we're circling.
我知道我現在在避免親密
I am fully aware that I am avoiding intimacy right now,
但一個女人試圖殺了我
but a woman tried to kill me,
一個年輕人因我犯的錯而死去
and a young man died from my mistakes.
在這一切中  我失去了我此生摯愛
And in all of this, I lost the love of my life
而他一開始就不屬于我
who was never mine to begin with.
我需要一些時間  才能接受共進晚餐和看電影
It's gonna take some time before I can handle a dinner and a movie.
但我無所謂
But I'm okay with that.
-知道為什么嗎  -為什么
- Do you know why? - Why?
因為過去四個月我不需要服藥
Because I've been going to sleep for the past four months
就能入睡
without taking any medication.
我不會聽到噪音而暴跳如雷
I don't jump at loud noises anymore.
我不會無緣無故大白天就哭起來
I don't cry in the middle of the day for no reason.
那墓地呢
And what about the cemetery?
你還每周都去給山姆掃墓嗎
Are you still visiting Sam's grave every week?
不  沒有了
No, I'm not.
卡莉花鋪
您需要什么嗎
Hi. Can I help you find something?
這些花很美  你覺得呢
Yeah. These look nice. What do you think?
你眼光很好  是什么特殊場合嗎
Great choice. Any special occasion?
送給我家寶貝的
Uh, well, they're for my lady.
洛杉磯還數你屁股最翹
You still have the best ass in L.A.
米基
Mickey!
你怎么來了
What are you doing here?
你不是要在意大利待到年底嗎
I thought you were in Italy until the end of the year.
在那里意粉吃夠了
Oh, there's only so much pasta one man can consume
再不回來就胖得沒男人要我了
before said man becomes so fat no other man will touch him.
給你的
Per te.
這家店看起來好棒
The store looks fantastic.
看來你不再需要我的財政資助了
I see my financial contributions are no longer necessary.
的確很棒  百無禁忌
Oh, it's been great. Knock on wood.
但沒有你的幫助  我絕對
But, you know, I never could have gotten here
做不到這樣
without your help.
我為你驕傲  接著怎么辦
I'm proud of you. So, what next?
什么意思
What do you mean?
開一家成功的小店  有了
Launched a successful business -- check.
但我沒看到這里有你的東西
But I still don't see any of your stuff here.
什么  你在說什么呢
What? What are you talking about?
這里都是我的東西啊
It's -- it's all my stuff.
我賣的東西都是我親手挑選的
I mean, I handpicked everything I sell.
我剛遇到了一位很棒的本地藝術家
In fact, I just met this cute local artist
她當時正在咖啡店展覽自己的作品  然后...
who was showcasing her work at this coffee house, and --
喂喂
Hello?
你才該是"很棒的本地藝術家"
You're supposed to be the cute local artist.
艾普莉·馬"超贊"洛伊
April Ma-freaking-lloy.
這不正是我們當初開店的初衷嗎
I thought that's why we opened this mini anthropologie.
我不再問你要錢你就該偷著樂了
You should just be happy I'm not taking money from you anymore.
我支持你的藝術時才最開心
Well, I was never happier than when I was supporting your art.
米基
Mickey...
我只是不想看你放棄
I just don't like to see you giving up.
你可是我黑人版的瑪莎·斯圖爾特[家政名人]
You're my black Martha Stewart.
我沒有放棄
I'm not giving up.
你得重獲你的魔力  親愛的
You need to get your mojo back, love.
明晚市區有個彈出式藝術展
Tomorrow night, there's a pop-up art show happening downtown.
我們一起去
We're going.
我不知道"彈出式"是什么意思
I'm not sure what "Pop-up" means,
但我的魔力可沒消失
but I don't think I lost any mojo.
親愛的  你都穿褲襪了
Sweetie, you're wearing jeggings.
你好啊  美人
Hello, gorgeous.
我可不喜歡受到這樣的歡迎
Okay, this is not how I like to be greeted.
好吧  有時我喜歡
O-okay, sometimes I like to be greeted that way.
這盆栽放屋里太大了
Apparently the pot is too big for the room.
這株植物挺好的啊
The plant is fine.
不過我個人會把那些雜七雜八的盤子都扔了
But, personally, I would ditch all those random plates.
我很樂意聽取你的意見
Yeah, I'd love to, uh, take your advice
來布置這間屋子  喬斯
on how to stage the house, Joss,
只可惜  你不是我的房產經紀人
but unfortunately, you're not my realtor.
你太不幸了
Ah, unfortunately for you.
我個人倒是很激動開始我的新職業
Personally, I'm thrilled to be starting a new career.
辦派對真的算是一種職業嗎
Does, uh, throwing parties actually constitute a career?
在洛杉磯可不就是了
It does if you live in Los Angeles.
這樣的話  不如交點租金啊
In that case, how about some rent?
你也才在這里住了  多久
You've only been living here for the past, whew, what is it?
十個月嘛
10 months?
關你什么事
W-what do you care?
你都一年多沒住這里了
You haven't lived here in over a year.
再說了  薩維說不用給
Besides, Savi said it was okay.
這屋子有一半歸我  而我說
Yeah, well, half the house belongs to me, and I say it's --
我說  無所謂了
I say... It doesn't matter.
反正馬上就搞定了
Be done with it soon enough.
她今天回家
She's home today.
我把她留在艾普莉店里了
I -- I left her back at April's,
不過她可能馬上就到家了
but she'll probably be here soon.
就  提醒你一下
Just -- just a heads up.
也許你該提醒她一下
Oh, maybe you should give her a heads up
我在這里做事呢
that I'm working here.
-還需要幾小時  -拜托  哈利
- Still need a few hours. - Oh, come on, Harry.
這事就不能等等嗎
Can't this stuff wait?
又不是得立馬賣了這屋子
It's not like you have to sell the house this second.
喬斯  我幾個月前就該
Actually, Joss, I needed to sell the house
把這屋子賣了的
a couple of months ago.
我的賬單都堆起來了  入賬卻越來越少
I got bills piling up and less money coming in.
你要她怎么辦
Well, what do you want her to do?
搬家壓力很大
You know, moving is crazy stressful,
她已經很脆弱了
and she's already so fragile.
她會想到辦法的  一向如此
She'll figure something out. She always does.
那是龐姬·布魯斯特[動畫片主角]嗎
Is that Punky Brewster?
閉嘴  走開點
Shh! Just go away!
你好啊  蘇蕾
Hi, Soleil.
幸會
Nice to meet you.
我叫喬斯琳  幸會  快請進吧
I'm Josslyn. Nice to meet you. Please come in.
這位是我朋友哈利·戴維斯
This is, uh, my friend Harry Davis.
-他正要走呢  -是嗎
- He was just leaving. - Was I?
哈利·戴維斯  我記得這名字
Harry Davis -- I know that name.
你是那個主廚
You're that chef.
你那家餐廳我去過好多次
I've been to your restaurant a million times.
叫什么來著  別告訴我
What's it called? Don't tell me. Don't tell me.
我知道的  叫...
I-I know it. It's, uh...
薩瓦娜
Savannah's.
薩瓦娜餐廳  超棒的
Savannah's Kitchen. Oh, it's fantastic.
曾經超棒的
Was fantastic.
我們  幾個月前關門了
We, uh -- we closed a couple of months ago.
不過很高興認識你
It's lovely meeting you, though.
-再見  -再見
- Cheers. - Bye.
好了  我說了
Okay, I'm gonna say it.
我很緊張
Uh, I was nervous.
真的  我緊張
I was. I was nervous.
你緊張
You were nervous?
為什么緊張
Why were you nervous?
我們又不是第一次做愛
It's not like - we haven't had sex before.
就在桌上做過一次
Uh, one time on a desk.
什么
What?
慢著  我們就做過那一次嗎
Wait. That was the only time we ever had sex?
除非把電話性愛也算進去
Unless you count the phone sex.
不不  那個不算
No. No, I can't count that.
我是假裝高潮的
I was faking it.
天哪  我真想你
Oh, God, I missed you.
真希望我能多溜出來幾次
I wish I could have come out more often.
已經夠多了
You came out plenty.
我知道這對你那瘋狂的
And I know that probably wasn't easy
工作日程來說很不容易  夢幻合伙人先生
with your crazy work schedule, Mr. Fancy Partner.
我的確很夢幻  這倒是真的
Oh, I am fancy. It's true.
不過說到工作
But, uh, speaking of work,
大家都在問你呢
everybody has been asking about you.
還沒人知道咱倆的事
And nobody knows about us yet,
所以你回律所時咱倆得
so we are gonna have to come up with a game plan
想個辦法
for when you come back.
前提是我會回去
When I come back.
你在計劃回來上班呢  不是嗎
You are planning on coming back, aren't you?
老實說  我在努力弄清
Honestly, I'm really just trying to figure out
自己該做什么  想做什么
what I should do and what I want to do.
我以為你熱愛你的工作呢
Yeah, but I thought you loved your job.
那是過去的薩維
The old Savi did.
但我不確定新生的薩維會不會喜歡
I'm just not sure the new Savi will.
我只是需要點時間  可以嗎
I just need some time. Is that okay?
我聽起來很瘋狂嗎
Do I sound crazy right now?
對
Yeah.
不過你很幸運  我喜歡瘋狂
But lucky for you, I dig crazy.
紀念醫院  急診部
你現在有在服用任何藥物嗎
And are you currently taking any medications?
維生素算嗎
Do vitamins count?
-不算  -那就沒有
- No. - Then no.
你今早離開家時
And when you left your house this morning,
你說過你要去上班  對嗎
you said you were going to work, is that right?
你在哪兒上班
And where do you work?
津巴布韋[非洲東南部國家]
Zimbabwe.
我在那兒跳舞
As a dancer.
轉去精神科
Turf to psych.
棒  贏了20塊
Yes! Just made 20 bucks.
你覺得用老年患者的
I'm not sure you should be gambling
心理健康狀況來押注好嗎
over the mental health of our elderly patients.
這是道格的主意
It was Doug's idea.
你還沒說今晚答不答應跟我一起吃晚餐呢
And you still didn't answer me about dinner tonight.
值班表已經排出來了  你不用隨時待命
Schedule just went up and you're not on call,
所以這個借口行不通
so you can't use that excuse.
我說過了  凱西  不行
I did answer you, Casey. I said no.
那是因為你以為今晚得工作  對嗎
Yeah, but that's 'cause you thought you had to work, right?
安娜  我是金醫生  抱歉讓你久等了
Hi, Anna. I'm Dr. Kim. Sorry to keep you waiting.
我都不知道還待在這兒干嘛
I don't even know what I'm still doing here.
他們已經把我的手腕固定好了
They already fixed my wrist.
你在這兒是因為護士
You're here because when the nurses
脫掉你的連帽運動衫時
removed your hooded sweatshirt,
看到你脖子上有捆綁的痕跡
they saw ligature marks around your neck.
你知道是什么時候有的嗎
Were you aware you had them?
知道
Yeah.
你可以解釋下是怎么弄得嗎
Can you explain how you got them?
我知道這感覺上像是侵犯隱私
I know this feels like an invasion of privacy,
但這完全是例行公事
but it's fairly routine.
你早點回答完我的問題
The sooner you answer my questions,
我就可以讓你早點回家
the sooner I can send you home.
我男朋友跟我今早做愛的時候弄得
My boyfriend and I were having sex this morning.
他喜歡粗暴點的
He likes it rough.
雙方都同意這種性行為嗎
Was the sex consensual?
當然了  他是我男朋友
Of course. He's my boyfriend.
他只是喜歡這種窒息的感覺
He's just into the whole asphyxiation thing.
沒那么變態
It's not that twisted.
你的手腕也是他扭傷的嗎
Is that how you sprained your wrist?
是的  但是
Yeah, but
這種情況告訴別人有點尷尬
that was kind of embarrassing to tell everyone.
所以我編造了拳擊的事
So I made up the boxing thing.
我能理解
I understand.
你男朋友現在在嗎
Is your boyfriend here now?
這里嗎  不在  他走了
Here? No. He's gone.
但是他載你來的
But he dropped you off.
是的  他馬上就得走
Yeah. He just had to leave, like, immediately.
他為一個混蛋做事
He works for this real jerk,
絕對不能遲到
and he can't be late, like, ever.
謝謝你  安娜
Hmm. Thank you, Anna.
我會叫護士來把手續辦完
I'll have a nurse come in to finish up the paperwork.
進行進一步評估
媽媽  你干嘛呢
Hey, mom. What you doing?
我在看這張桌子
I'm looking at this desk.
它做什么錯事了嗎
Did it do something wrong?
它對我來說毫無用處
It's doing nothing for me.
這才是問題  它只是一張普通的白桌子
That's the problem. It's just a boring white desk.
如果不是呢
What if it wasn't?
如果
What if...
如
What...
果
if...
你這是中風了嗎
Are you having a stroke?
你知道我生你之前是做什么的嗎
Do you know what I used to do before I had you?
搞藝術的
Art.
我小時候的理想是當一名藝術家
I wanted to be an artist when I grew up.
我想做人們需要的東西
Mostly, I wanted to make things people needed,
但要想方設法讓它們變得漂亮
but find a way to make them beautiful.
就像這張桌子
Like this desk, for instance.
它可以變得很特別
It could be something special.
怎么變
How?
我不知道
I don't know.
這就證明米基是對的
Which means Mickey was right.
我的魔力不在了
I lost my mojo.
你現在說的話我只能聽懂一半
I only understand like half the words you're saying right now.
抱歉  親愛的
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
你呢  新學校怎么樣
How are you? How's the new school?
還不錯
It's fine.
我今天找了張午餐桌旁坐下
Today, I sat down at a lunch table
每個人都在討論《饑餓游戲》
where everyone was talking about "Hunger Games."
所以我也開始參與討論
So I started talking about it, too,
沒人覺得奇怪
and no one thought it was weird.
所以我就留下了
So I stayed.
露西  你學習很努力  獲得了洛杉磯
Lucy, you worked hard and you got a scholarship
最昂貴學校之一的獎學金
into one of the fanciest schools in L.A.
你跟她們坐在一起  是那些姑娘的幸運
Those girls are lucky you sat at their table.
也有男孩在
There were boys there, too.
你這是想嚇唬我吧
See, now you're just trying to freak me out.
我還不到40歲  已經開始第四段事業了
I'm not even 40, and I'm already on my fourth career.
關鍵是  如果有些事出了問題
The point is, if something isn't working,
其實這只是個讓你嘗試新事物的機會
it's simply an opportunity to try something new.
永遠別懼怕進化
Never be afraid to evolve.
姐們兒  你這是班門弄斧了
Sister, you are preaching to the choir.
我無時無刻不在進化
I'm all about evolving right now.
實際上我就是這么干起聚會策劃的
It's actually how I got into party planning.
你是剛開始嗎
Yeah, now, did you just start?
我這么問只是因為你的簡歷有點單薄
I only ask because your resume's a little thin.
我干了六個月左右了
I've been doing it for six months or so,
得到了一些滿意的反饋
but I've gotten some great feedback,
如果你要的話我有大量的推薦
and I have a ton of referrals if you want.
但我不想浪費你的時間
But I don't want to waste your time
談論其他人的派對
talking about other people's parties.
我寧愿談談你的
I'd much rather talk about yours.
我也是
Me, too.
好的  首先  這些絲巾漂亮的要死
Okay, so, first of all, these scarves are to die.
我每一條都想要
I want every single one of them.
但愿吧  派對過后
Well, hopefully, after this party,
你可以買下來
you'll be able to buy them.
我們要邀請所有的高端買家
So we're gonna invite all the top buyers,
所以我們得竭盡全力
which is why we have to go balls to the wall.
寶貝兒  這是我的強項
Honey, balls is what I do best.
好的
Okay.
訂花的花店和廚師我有很多可以推薦的
So, and I have a ton of options for florists and caterers.
我從前面給你展示吧
Let me actually just take you through from the beginning.
我們循序漸進的來  好嗎
We'll go step-by-step, shall we?
我一回到辦公室就把這些上傳
I'll get these uploaded as soon as I get back to the office
為放映幻燈片選選音樂
and pick some music for the slide show.
除非你已經想好了
Unless you had a preference.
不  我更想讓你盡快
No, I prefer you sell this house
以最高價賣掉這棟房子
as quickly as possible for as much money as you can.
好極了
Fantastic.
哈利  很抱歉
Harry, I'm so sorry.
我不知道你在這
I didn't know you'd be here.
我是薩維
Hi, I'm Savi.
瓦妮莎·克羅斯  我是你的地產經紀
Vanessa Cross -- your realtor.
瓦妮莎
Hi, Vanessa.
終于見到你本人了  真好
It's so nice to finally meet you in -- in person.
這廚房看起來真不錯
The kitchen looks beautiful.
我們照了些很好的照片
We got some great pictures.
我得走了  咱們保持聯絡
I should go. We'll be in touch.
好
Okay.
謝謝你
Thank you.
哈利  我很抱歉
Harry, I'm so sorry.
喬斯提過你可能在這
Joss mentioned that you might be here,
但是我沒看到車道上有你的車
but I didn't see your car in the driveway,
我應該先打個電話的
So I-I just should've called first.
不用  有個朋友來接我
No, I got a friend picking me up.
她來了
Here she is now.
寶貝
Hey, babe.
準備好吃晚餐了嗎
You ready for dinner?
餓死了
Starved.
歡迎回家
Hey. Welcome home.
我真的希望你別那樣做
I really wish you wouldn't do that.
我很高興你在這里
I'm just so happy you're here.
你應該經常在我這里過夜
You should always sleep over.
那樣我們就可以每天早晨做愛了
Then we could have morning sex every day.
多有樂趣啊
Wouldn't that be so much fun?
是的  是很有趣
Yeah, that -- that would be fun.
但是那樣我留下來過夜就不顯得特別了
Um, but then it wouldn't be as special when I do stay over.
這就是收益遞減法則
It's the law of diminishing returns.
基本的經濟原理
Basic economic principle.
我可以使它特別
I could make it special.
真的嗎
Really?
怎么做到呢
How?
明白了
I see.
好的  我會每天來過夜
Yep.I'll do it.
不要介意
Don't mind me.
我穿了我的新赫爾姆特·朗夾克和靴子
I'm just wearing my new Helmut Lang jacket and boots.
你好靴子  我會借你來穿的
Well, hello, boots. I will be borrowing you.
天啊  等等
Oh, my God. Wait.
這意味著你得到龐姬·布魯斯特的工作了
Does this mean you got the Punky Brewster job?
還沒有
Okay, I didn't get it just yet.
另外  我們不應該那么叫她
And, P.S., we're not allowed to call her that.
但我一定會得到的  我們太合得來了
But it's for sure gonna happen. We totally hit it off.
太好了  喬斯  我真為你高興
That is so great, Joss. I'm so happy for you.
她的電話  噓噓噓
It's her. Shh. Shh. Shh.
你好  我是喬斯琳
Hello. This is Josslyn.
你好喬斯  我是蘇蕾
Hey, Joss. It's Soleil.
我想告訴你
I just wanted to let you know
我找別人了
that I'm going with someone else.
但我還是想打給你  因為我真的非常喜歡你
But I wanted to call because I really, really like you.
你只是有點經驗不足
You're just a little too green.
但我以為你喜歡正在發展的人
But I -- I thought you celebrated people evolving.
我是的  但我也在發展就不行了
I do. Just not when I'm evolving.
我給你小建議好嗎
Can I make a little suggestion?
你需要一個團隊
You need a team --
你能帶著的一群你了解并且信任的人
A stable of people you know and trust that you can bring with you.
給人看一堆亂七八糟的簡歷太讓人頭疼了
It's overwhelming to be handed a giant stack of random resumes.
我聘用一個派對策劃人的原因
The whole reason I hire party planners
就是我不用看那些亂七八糟的簡歷
is so that I don't have to look at random resumes.
有道理  謝謝你考慮我
That makes sense. Thanks for considering me.
傻帽龐姬·布魯斯特
Stupid Punky Brewster.
別別別  別把唇膏沾到我的外套上
No, no, no. Don't get lipstick on my jacket.
-我還得還回去  -你不用
- I have to take it back. - No, you don't. No.
就當是對你未來的投資
Consider it an investment in your future.
再說  你今晚可以穿
Plus, you can wear it tonight.
-今晚有什么事  -市區的藝術秀
- What's tonight? - That art show downtown.
我跟你說過了  薩維和凱倫也來
I told you about it. Savi and Karen are coming, too.
我不知道
I don't know.
我想回家自艾自憐
I kind of want to go home and feel crappy about myself.
不行  你可以明天再自艾自憐
No, no. You can feel crappy about yourself tomorrow.
今晚  我們要盛裝打扮  找到我的魔力
Tonight, we are getting all dolled up, finding my mojo,
你要打扮得靚麗
And you are gonna look fabulous.
今天我們怎么做  和往常一樣嗎
So, what are we doing today? Same as usual?
只要別剪短
If it ain't broke.
你好
Hello.
是我
Hey. It's, uh, it's me.
你好
Hey, you.
聽著  我得取消今天的午餐約會了
Listen, I'm gonna have to cancel our lunch date today.
和我一起工作的合伙人  托尼
The associate I've been working with, Tony,
被這單案子搞得不堪重負
is completely overwhelmed with this case.
沒關系  不用擔心
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
我只是
I just...
我討厭這樣
I hate this.
我不想做那種因為工作而取消約會的人
I don't want to be the guy who cancels because of work.
不  你不是那種人
No, you're not.
-我很抱歉  -真的沒關系
- I am sorry. - It's totally okay.
晚些再打給你
Call you later?
-好的  -好  再見
- Sounds good. - All right, bye.
準備好了
Ready?
你猜怎樣
You know what?
我們試試別的
Let's try something different.
是嗎  你想怎么弄
Oh, yeah? What'd you have in mind?
有人有她的消息嗎
Has anyone even heard from her?
確定她會來嗎
Are we sure she's coming?
她今天早晨告訴我她會來
she told me this morning she'd be here,
可能我太強求她了
but maybe it was too much.
好吧  我再給她發個短信
Okay, let me text her again.
你們覺得如何
So, what do you think?
太好了
A-mazeballs.
我找不到薩維了
I lost Savi.
很正常  她太矮了
It happens. She's very small.
她也許在吧臺
Maybe she's at the bar.
天哪
Oh, crap.
怎么啦
What? What's wrong?
我確定我睡過那個人
I'm pretty sure I slept with that guy.
多少次
How many times?
一次半  我閃了
Like 1 1/2? On the move.
謝天謝地
Thank God.
我正要去車里等著
I was about to go wait in the car.
你什么時候開始喜歡派對了
Since when don't you like parties?
一直都喜歡啊  你不記得中學舞會了
Since always. - Do you not remember junior prom?
看啊  一只梨  太有意義了
Oh, look. A pear. How meaningful.
渲染得不錯
Oh, that's a nice rendering.
梨嗎  真的是
Of a pear, sure.
如果我有天分  我就會那樣做
That's what I would do if I had talent --
閑坐無事畫畫水果
sit around drawing freaking fruit.
那個很好
Now, that's something.
事實上美極了
It's kind of stunning, actually.
是的
It sure is.
天啊
Oh, my lord.
天哪  天哪  天哪
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
什么
What?
薩維去哪了
Where's Savi?
不知道
Not sure.
她剛才在庭審一群二十幾歲的年輕人
She was holding court with a bunch of 20-somethings
人家在聊聊莉娜·杜漢姆
who were talking about Lena Dunham.
美劇《都市女孩》的主演
你還好嗎
You okay?
也許我該堅持在地產行業干下去
Maybe I should've stuck to real estate.
至少我擅長那個
At least I was good at that.
別對自己太苛刻
Don't be so hard on yourself.
那這是你第一次被拒絕
It's your first rejection.
凱倫  我努力了六個月
Karen, I've been going at this for six months,
唯一的一份工作還是朋友可憐我
and the only jobs I've gotten are from friends who pity me.
那些以前羨慕我的朋友
My friends who used to want to be me
現在看到我都會一臉同情
are now giving me sad face.
我也變成那種女孩了
I'm that girl now.
哪種女孩兒
Which girl?
還沒長大的哪種
The girl who still hasn't grown up.
我快30了  實際上卻失業
I mean, I'm almost 30, and I'm practically unemployed.
和姐姐一起住  還沒結婚
I live with my sister. I'm not married.
你什么時候也想結婚了
Since when do you want to be married?
我不想結婚
Mnh-mnh. I don't.
我只是說  想讓自己變得更好
I'm just saying, I want to be...more.
比現在的我更加豐富
I just -- I want to be more than what I am now.
我想加入一個團隊
I want a -- I want a freaking team.
和哈利談談  他在那一行里
Talk to Harry. He's in that world.
我肯定他認識不少人
I'm sure he knows people.
還真是個還不錯的主意
You know, that's actually not the worst idea.
你就該以幫助別人為生
You should help people for a living.
你很擅長這個
You're pretty good at it.
你好
Oh. Hello.
艾普-
Apr--
還好嗎
Is everything okay?
我太渴了
I'm very thirsty.
你看起來很焦慮
You look agitated.
我有感覺了
I'm having feelings.
什么感覺
What kind of feelings?
艾普莉  你藏在角落里干什么
April, what are you doing hiding in the corner?
她有感覺了
She's having feelings.
-你和他聊天了嗎  -和誰
- Have you talked to him yet? - Talked to who?
-沒誰  -跟我來
- Nobody. - Come with me.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
淡定  我們去跳舞
Calm down. We're just gonna dance.
真有趣  你真逗
That's funny. You're funny.
這叫策略  如果你不去找他
It's called strategy. If you don't go to him,
那就讓他主動找你
we got to make him come to you.
-誰啊  -性感悶騷男
- Who? - Sexy smoldering.
-誰啊  -布蘭奇  桃樂絲  快閉嘴
- Who? - Blanche, Dorothy, zip it.
羅思和我有事要做
Rose and I have business to attend to.
她太像羅思了[布蘭奇 桃樂絲 羅思均出自《綠野仙蹤》]
She's so Rose.
開始跳吧
Here we go.
你瘋了
You are insane.
承認吧  你想我了
Admit it. You miss me.
他在看嗎
Is he looking?
我找不到他  我也不知道
I can't find him. I don't know.
-我們要停下嗎  -不要
- Should we stop? - Umm.
她也不在盥洗室
She's not in the bathroom.
太奇怪了  我已經給她發了無數短信
This is insane. I've sent her like 100 texts.
很抱歉  醫院又有事了
So sorry, but work called.
但如果你需要我的話  我可以...
Uh, but if you need me to stay, I'll --
老天
Oh, my god.
怎么了
What?
新薩維正在自拍
The new Savi takes selfies.
看起來她玩的很開心
Looks like she's having a good time.
她在哪
Where is she?
你要走了
Oh, you leaving?
我要回醫院去一趟
I got to get back to the hospital.
有點緊急情況
There's some sort of emergency.
在急診工作肯定會有緊急事件
That's what happens when you work in an E.R. -- Emergencies.
抱歉  我喝醉了
I'm sorry. I'm drunk.
要送你嗎
Did you need a ride?
沒事  我打車
No, that's okay. I'll grab an uber.
不用  我也精疲力盡  我應該和你一起走
No, I'm pretty wiped out, too. I should -- I should go with you.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
米基會載你回家
Mickey will take you home later
在你和性感悶騷男聊天之后
after you talk to sexy smoldering.
不不  我不行
No, no, no. I can't.
想再去和豬玩嗎
Do you want to pet another pig?
她已經差不多了  我要載她回家
Uh, she's at the standard. I'm gonna go pick her up.
不想讓她病好后第一晚出來玩就玩太過
I don't want her overdoing it on her first night out.
對沒有長大的人來說
You know, - for someone who hasn't grown up,
你看起來像我們小團體新的輔導員
you sure seem like the new den mother of the group.
說不定你是對的
Hmm. Maybe you're right.
有點像安吉麗娜·朱莉
You know, it's kind of like how Angelina
她曾是個和自己哥哥有親密關系的女孩
used to be the chick - who made out with her brother,
現在她收養了快100個孩子
and now she has like 100 kids
還在做防治乳腺癌方面的演講
and speaks out for breast cancer.
就是那樣
It's exactly like that.
它叫露西亞
That one's called Lucia.
我是丹尼爾
I'm Daniel.
艾普莉
April.
你的作品很美
Your work is beautiful.
謝謝  很高興你喜歡
Thanks. I'm glad you like it.
木頭對我來說是種新媒介
Um, wood is a, it's a new medium for me.
我更熟悉顏料和丙烯畫
I'm more comfortable with paints, acrylics,
不過我想  是我該走出
but, uh, I thought it was about time
舒適帶的時候了
I broke out of my comfort zone.
我也是
Me, too.
這就是我來這的原因
I mean, that -- that's why I'm here.
舒適帶  魔力
Comfort zones, mojo.
-你今晚有展示嗎  -我  不不
- So you're showing tonight? - Me? No. No.
我現在不再搞藝術了
I'm not currently creating art.
但我會為我的店鋪添置藝術品
But I do buy art for my store.
我有個小店
I have a store.
也為家里買藝術品  但主要是為了店里賣
I also buy for my -- my house, but I sell from my -- my store.
或許明天你能來我工作室
Well, maybe you can come by my studio tomorrow
看看我其他的作品
and see some of my other collections.
說不定在你店里或者房子里能用
You know, they might work in your store or your house.
好的
Okay.
可以啊
Um, yeah. I could do that.
給
Uh...Here.
這是一次約會
It's a date.
別麻煩了
Don't bother.
三個醫生  一大堆透視檢查
Three doctors, a bunch of B.S. scans,
還有社會福利工作者  就為治療手腕扭傷
and a social worker all for a sprained wrist?
多會騙人啊
What a scam.
社會福利工作者是我要求的
I requested the social worker.
你
You?
為什么
Why?
因為你脖子上的痕跡
Because of the marks on your neck.
這樣我們可以排除虐待
So we could rule out abuse.
老天
Oh, my god.
我告訴過你  我男友愛我
I told you, my boyfriend loves me.
他不會傷害我的
He'd never hurt me.
-他來接你嗎  -是的
- Is he coming to pick you up? - Yes.
[韓語]真的嗎
[韓語]信不信由你
這就是真相
It's the truth.
哪個部分
Which part?
你和你男友的性愛游戲
The sex games with your boyfriend
還是你有個所謂的男朋友
or the fact that you have a boyfriend at all?
[韓語]我會幫助你的
[韓語]有我在  不要擔心
安娜  有人傷害你嗎
Anna, did someone do this to you?
還是你自己干的
Did you do this to you?
你確定喜歡這個花商
So, you definitely love this florist?
百分之百  珍是我唯一會用的人
100%. Jen's the only person I'll use.
好的  那酒席承辦方面呢
Okay. What about, um, caterers?
對對
Uh, yep. Yep.
我問了一圈
I asked around,
現在唯一有空閑的兩個廚師
and the only two chefs who are available right now
一個是我去年辭退的助理馬可
are that guy Marco who I fired as my sous last year --
既然你之前都把他炒了
Well, if you fired him,
那我為什么還要請他
why would I want to work with him?
可以不請
Well, you wouldn't.
我只是告訴你可以請到哪些人
Just telling you who's available.
好吧  還有誰
Okay, well, who's the other guy?
我
Me.
你是開玩笑的  對吧
You're joking, right?
有什么不行
Well, why not?
你需要廚師
You need a caterer.
我可能是這城市里最好的大廚
I'm arguably one of the best chefs in this city.
關鍵詞是"可能"
Key word -- "arguably."
而且我們之前也合作過
And we've done it before.
什么時候
When?
還記得那座詭異的房子嗎
Remember that weird house
就是把馬桶放在客廳中間的那座
with the toilet in the middle of the living room?
多虧了我你才化解了那次危機
You solved that monstrosity because of me.
我可不覺得你能讓這些女人滿意
I don't think you're giving the ladies nearly enough credit.
就當是權宜之計  好吧
Consider it a stopgap, okay?
等我雇的獵頭公司
Till the headhunters I hired get off their asses
幫我找到好的工作之后再說
and find me a solid gig.
好吧  你現在太挑剔了  哈利
Okay, now, you're being picky, Harry,
因為原來那家...
Because that place on Ivar was...
那是我單打獨斗
It was me working a line.
我不想再單打獨斗了
I'm not about to go back to working a line.
我們聊這些有什么意義
Okay, why are we even having this conversation?
很顯然我們不能一起工作
Obviously, you and I cannot work together.
為什么不能
Why not?
你知道的
Because you know why not.
因為我姐姐
Because of my sister
而且你還在恨她
And the fact that you still hate her.
所以呢
So?
所以這是個問題
So it's a problem.
說真的  你還在恨她嗎
And, seriously, you still hate her?
這只是工作
It's just business.
喬斯  我們的個人情感不會對這有影響的
Joss, our personal feelings don't have to come into play at all.
現在不會  但以后會  哈利
No, no, no. But they will, Harry.
我就要不得不選邊站
And I'll be forced to choose sides,
一切都會變得很麻煩
and it'll get all complicated.
我現在可不想要那種壓力
And I don't need that stress right now.
這  這對我來說是全新的職業  我...
This is... this is a brand-new business for me, and I-I just...
我可不想再有什么家庭鬧劇牽扯進去
I don't want to add any extra family drama to it.
你明白的  對吧
You understand that, don't you?
對  隨便吧
Yeah, whatever.
只是我的想法
Just an idea.
我來問問你今早感覺怎么樣
Just wanted to see how you were feeling this morning.
挺好
Okay.
比昨天好
Better than yesterday.
謝謝你昨晚留下來陪我聊了那么久
Thanks for staying and talking for so long last night.
聊天能夠幫你渡過這難關  安娜
Talking is what's gonna get you through this, Anna.
我很高興你能接受別人的幫助
I'm proud of you for accepting help.
我知道你要去看亞歷山大醫生
And I saw that you're meeting with Dr. Alexander.
他很出色
He's excellent.
你找對人了
You'll be in great hands.
等一下  什么  我以為你才是我的醫生
Wait. What? - I-I thought you were my doctor.
在急診室  我是
In the E.R., I am.
不幸的是  我已經有好幾個月
Unfortunately, I haven't worked in private practice
-沒有在私人診所做過了  -你開玩笑呢
- for several months. - Are you kidding me?
我要去跟我根本不認識的陌生人聊
I have to talk to some random guy I don't even know?
算了吧
Forget it.
如果你想要選別人  比如女性醫生
If you prefer to choose someone else, a female perhaps...
不用了
I'm not doing it.
我理解你現在很失意
I understand you're frustrated right now.
但是你能否出院
But your release from the hospital
取決于你是否愿意接受治療
is dependent on your willingness to accept treatment.
如果你不接受
If you don't follow through,
他們可能會一直讓你
they may opt to hold you until...
然后呢  我沒得選了
So what? I have no choice?
你騙我向你說出實話
You tricked me into telling you the truth,
結果我現在被困在這了
And now I'm just stuck here?
如果你誤解了  我很抱歉
I'm sorry if you misunderstood.
-滾出我房間  -拜托  安娜
- Get out of my room. - Please, Anna...
快走
Just go!
求你了  走吧
Please, just go!
求你了
Please, just...
我拿了你的浴簾桿
I took your curling iron.
在衛生間里
It's in the bathroom.
沒事  用完再還我
No problem. I'll get it later.
我還打印了幾份晚飯的菜譜
And I also printed out some recipes for tonight.
我想親自下廚
I thought I'd cook for us.
好的  如果你冥想完了想跟我聊天
Okay, but if you want to talk to me when you're done meditating,
-隨時都行  -沒事  沒事
- I'm totally around. - It's fine. It's fine.
我能一心二用
I'm multitasking.
就是臉上洋溢著各種表情
Multitasking sort of flies in the face
然后心里還能獲得平靜  是吧
of achieving inner peace, no?
你知道哈利跟凱拉好上了嗎
Did you know that Harry was dating Kyra?
別誤會我
I mean, don't get me wrong.
我很高興他戀愛了  可那是凱拉
I'm glad he's dating, but it's just Kyra.
這...  我也說不好
It just... I don't know.
感覺選擇她好奇怪
It just seems like such a weird choice.
這就是你冥想的原因嗎
Okay, is this why you're meditating?
不
Oh, no.
我在冥想是因為現在才11點
I'm meditating because it's 11:00
可我已經去完了超市  鍛煉完了
and I've already been to the supermarket, worked out,
還洗完了衣服  打掃完了車庫
done the laundry, and cleaned out the garage.
我真的不擅長無所事事
I'm really not good at this down-time thing.
我還有壞消息
I've got bad news for you.
你也很不擅長冥想
You are not very good at meditating, either.
我的天  我知道
Oh, my God. I know.
其實  我冥想得最差了
I'm the worst, actually.
這根本不行
This whole thing is not working.
什么  什么不行
What? What is not working?
我不工作是不行的
Me not working isn't working.
那就回去工作唄
So go back to work.
我不確定自己是不是還應該當律師
Well, I'm just not sure I should still be a lawyer.
或許新的薩維應該嘗試一下別的工作
I mean, maybe new Savi should try something new.
-比如什么  -不知道
- Like what? - I don't know.
有沒有別的什么工作既能盤問別人
Is there another job that I could cross-examine people
又能經常大喊"我反對"
and yell "I object" a lot?
因為我很喜歡這樣
Because I do really enjoy that.
我也很滿意我的薪資水平
I also really enjoy the amount I get paid.
所以我們應該也把這考慮在內
So we should probably factor that in, too.
沒錯
Right.
好吧  個人拙見
Okay, so, tiny thought.
隨便說說
Just spit-balling here.
或許你想不到有什么新的美好生活
Maybe you're having a really hard time imagining this new life
是因為你以前的生活并非不好  薩維
because the old one wasn't that bad, Sav.
是約炮短信嗎
Is that a sext?
-你昨天晚上釣到誰了  -別別別  薩維
- Did you hook up last night? - No, no, no, no. Savi, wait.
這是誰的孩子
Whose baby is this?
艾琳·薩爾茲曼
Erin Salzman.
前幾天我給她的寶寶辦了聚會
I did her, uh, baby shower a few days ago.
對不起
I'm sorry.
為什么道歉
Why are you sorry?
因為  我...
Just 'cause... I don't...
我們沒談過這事
We haven't talked about it, and...
我不知道我該怎么說
I don't know what I'm supposed to say.
我不想哭  因為我知道你不喜歡
I don't want to cry, because I know you hate that.
沒關系的  親愛的
It's okay, sweetie.
我沒事
I'm okay.
-你確定  -是的
- You sure? - Yeah.
我只是希望你早點告訴我派對那事
I just wish you would've told me about the shower.
我真的為你驕傲
I'm really proud of you.
別太驕傲了
Well, don't be too proud,
因為我差點就搞砸了
because it's all on the verge of exploding in my face.
哈利前幾天說想幫我準備宴會的食物
Harry asked if he could be my caterer the other day.
他是瘋了對吧
That's nuts, right?
他是我知道的最棒的廚師
He's the best chef I know.
如果這樣他會高興  天哪  喬斯
And if it makes him happy -- oh, God, Joss.
我就只想讓他高興
I mean, that's all I want.
你是個好人  查理·布朗[漫畫人物]
You are a good man, Charlie Brown.
難說
Hardly.
現在如果你不介意的話
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要繼續追求內心的平靜了
I'm going to continue pursuing inner peace.
好  我馬上走  愛你
Ah, yes. Leaving. Love you.
愛你
Love you.
我真希望我的靈感來源于
I wish I could say I was inspired
某個藝術家或者某副著名的畫作
by a particular artist or famous painting,
但說實話
But, truthfully,
最讓我震撼的還是日常生活中的種種
I'm mostly struck by things I see every day.
如果我對光更敏感
You know, if I had any aptitude with light,
我會進攝影界
I'd venture into photography,
但是我沒那個天分
but I'm just not that gifted.
我覺得你很有天分啊
You seem pretty gifted to me.
我沒想到會接到你的電話
I was surprised when you called.
很高興  但很意外
Happy, but surprised.
為什么  我說過我會打的
Why? I said I would.
大多數人都是言行不一
Most people never do what they say they're gonna do.
至少從我的經驗來說是這樣的
At least, that's been my experience.
如果我說話不算數  那就一無是處了
Well, I am nothing if not true to my word.
你絕對不是一無是處
I think you're a lot more than that.
其實  你沒那么了解我
I mean, you don't know me very well.
或許  我可以去了解你
Maybe...I could get to know you.
這話...
That sounds...
我可能喜歡
I might like that.
所以你基本上就是
So, basically, you cook the chicken
把雞肉用塑料袋裝著在水里煮的
in a plastic bag and put it under water.
Sous-vide意思就是"在水里"
Sous-vide -- that means "under water."
其實是"真空"的意思
Actually, it means "under vacuum."
為什么是"真空"的意思
Why would it mean "under vacuum"
明明是在水里煮的啊
when I'm cooking it under water?
道理很對  肉也很好吃
You make a great point, and an excellent meat.
我還帶了甜點呢
W-well, I -- I brought dessert, too.
算了  我一點都吃不下了
No. I couldn't possibly eat any more.
我飽了  但還是謝謝你過來
I am stuffed. But thank you for coming by.
-我會聯系你的  -好
- I'll be in touch. - Okay.
-你知道我的郵箱嗎  -知道
- You've got my e-mail? - I do.
-很好  -謝謝
- Fantastic. - Thank you.
哈利  是我
Harry, hey. It's me.
你還想當我的廚師嗎
Any chance you still want to be my chef?
我從沒見過有人這么討厭一件家具
I've never seen anyone hate a piece of furniture so bad.
這是打磨  孩子  打磨它
It's good hate, baby. Good hate.
對了  過來
You know what? Come here.
你戴上這個
Okay, I want you to put these on.
戴上
Put them on.
好
There you go.
像這樣使勁把這個敲碎
Want you to smash this like that.
我們做馬賽克
We're doing a mosaic.
馬賽克是什么
What's a mosaic?
一會兒你就知道了
You'll see.
你讓我打碎東西嗎
You want me to break stuff?
有時為了制作新東西是需要打碎舊的
Sometimes you got to break stuff to make stuff.
打吧
Go ahead.
你是不是已經找到你的魔力了
Does this mean you found your mojo?
你想知道嗎
Wouldn't you like to know?
你還有什么想說的嗎
Is there anything else you'd like to talk about today?
其實我想知道  你覺得
I was actually wondering how much longer
這種治療還需要持續多久
you think these sessions will be necessary.
這完全取決于你
It's entirely up to you.
如果你覺得治療沒用...
If you're not finding them helpful...
不  有用
No, I have.
你一直做得很好  布萊克利醫生
You've been wonderful, Dr. Blakeley.
只是現在  我...
It's just that, right now, I'm...
你需要休息一下
You need a break.
我知道我面對的是什么
I know what I'm up against.
如果我想更進一步的話
And if I'm gonna push through to the next level,
我覺得我需要自己去做
I think I need to do it alone.
至少讓我自己試試
At least for a little while.
我依舊同意你的評估  金醫生
As usual, I agree with your assessment, Dr. Kim.
有需要盡管找我
I'm always here if you need me.
謝謝
Thank you.
還有件事
There is one thing.
我覺得應該讓你知道
I think you'd like to know
我決定重新開始做私人醫生了
that I've decided to start up on my private practice again.
真的嗎  為什么改主意了
Really? What changed your mind?
我遇見了個人
I met someone.
喂  安娜  我是金醫生
Hi, Anna. It's Dr. Kim.
如果你還沒選好醫生的話
If you haven't already chosen a doctor,
我明天可以幫你看看
I have some time for a session tomorrow.
你想來的話記得跟我說
Let me know if you'd like to talk.
不  忙著呢
Nope. Busy.
這就當起尖酸刻薄的合伙人了啊
So you're the mean partner?
不好意思  請問你是哪位
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
你怎么來了
I didn't know you were coming.
說實話我是來找你一起吃晚餐的
Well, technically, I'm here to steal you away for dinner.
但是鑒于我們還沒公開
But since we're not out of the closet,
所以名義上我是來跟大家打招呼的
officially, I'm here to say hi to everyone.
還有跟米切爾說一聲
And to let Mitchell know
我準備好回來上班了
that I think I'm ready to come back to work.
真的嗎
Really?
真的
Yeah.
我想先從兼職工作開始
Well, I thought I'd start out part time
看看感覺如何
and just see how it feels.
除非  我也不知道
Unless...I don't know.
你覺得  覺得怎么樣  不好嗎
What do you -- what do you think? Bad idea?
不  我覺得你這樣很好
No, I think it's a brilliant idea.
說真的  我都想緊緊抱住你
In fact, I, uh, kind of want to wrap you up in my arms
用行動告訴你這樣有多棒
and show you just how brilliant an idea it is.
就在此時此地
Right here, right now.
好像開始我們就是這樣惹上麻煩的
I think that's what got us in trouble in the first place,
如果沒記錯的話
if I recall.
等等  你想什么時候回來
Wait. Uh, w-when are you thinking of starting back?
下周吧  怎么了
Next week. Why?
沒事
It's no big deal.
你離開后我們這里減員了
It's just that, you know, we downsized since you left
三層少了幾間辦公室
and lost some of the offices on the third floor.
所以幾個合伙人現在共用辦公室辦公
So a few of the associates are sharing space.
沒事
Well, no big deal.
反正我也不是全職  共用辦公室合情合理
Half the work, half the space. Seems fair to me.
那就好
Great.
要見見你的新室友嗎  托尼
Want to go meet your new roommate, Tony.
我跟你說起過的那個
The one I've been telling you about?
-無聊鬼托尼嗎  -對
- Tony the time suck? - Yeah.
那你的晚餐時間
Yeah, I'm gonna have to explain that your dinner hours
要變得更加神圣了
are about to become more sacred.
托尼
Toni.
你好  老板
Hello, boss.